import { MCQuestionType, TFQuestionType } from "../types";

export const hardMC: MCQuestionType[] = [
  {
    question:
      "Which NBA team is known for its 'Run TMC' era in the early 1990s?",
    choices: [
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "San Antonio Spurs",
    ],
    correct: "Golden State Warriors",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which NBA player is known for his nickname 'The Round Mound of Rebound'?",
    choices: [
      "Karl Malone",
      "Shaquille O'Neal",
      "Charles Barkley",
      "Dennis Rodman",
    ],
    correct: "Charles Barkley",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team won the first-ever NBA Championship in 1947?",
    choices: [
      "Chicago Stags",
      "Philadelphia Warriors",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "New York Knicks",
    ],
    correct: "Philadelphia Warriors",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the most points scored by a player in a single NBA game without missing a field goal?",
    choices: ["38 points", "42 points", "40 points", "55 points"],
    correct: "42 points",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which team is the sixth NBA team to win Game 7 after leading a series 3-1?",
    choices: [
      "Milwaukee Bucks",
      "Utah Jazz",
      "Los Angeles Clippers",
      "Oklahoma City Thunder",
    ],
    correct: "Los Angeles Clippers",
  },
  {
    question: 'Which team fanbase chanted "Wife Beater!" to Jason Kidd?',
    choices: [
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Philadelphia 76ers",
      "Utah Jazz",
    ],
    correct: "Boston Celtics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which team did Toronto Raptors general manager Masai Ujiri make derogotary remarks against?",
    choices: [
      "Brooklyn Nets",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "New York Knicks",
      "Philadelphia 76ers",
    ],
    correct: "Brooklyn Nets",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these players attended Florida State?",
    choices: ["Mason Plumlee", "Terance Mann", "Julius Randle", "Aaron Gordon"],
    correct: "Terance Mann",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team drafted Michael Derek Jackson in the second round?",
    choices: [
      "Los Angeles Clippers",
      "Sacramento Kings",
      "New York Knicks",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
    ],
    correct: "New York Knicks",
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the first overall pick in the 1989 NBA draft?",
    choices: ["Tim Hardaway", "Glen Rice", "Danny Ferry", "Pervis Ellison"],
    correct: "Pervis Ellison",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team relocated in the 1985-86 NBA season?",
    choices: [
      "Brooklyn Nets",
      "Sacramento Kings",
      "Oklahoma City Thunder",
      "Charlotte Hornets",
    ],
    correct: "Sacramento Kings",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was selected in the first round by the Sacramento Kings in the 1088 NBA draft?",
    choices: ["Ricky Berry", "Reggie Theus", "LaSalle Thompson", "Joe Kleine"],
    correct: "Ricky Berry",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team did Spud Webb play for?",
    choices: [
      "Los Angeles Clippers",
      "Atlanta Hawks",
      "Detroit Pistons",
      "Indiana Pacers",
    ],
    correct: "Atlanta Hawks",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player finished second on the team in scoring with 17.1 points per game for the 1999-2000 Timberwolves?",
    choices: [
      "Wally Szczerbiak",
      "Anthony Peeler",
      "Terrell Brandon",
      "Sam Mitchell",
    ],
    correct: "Terrell Brandon",
  },
  {
    question: "Who was traded for Kevin Love after the 2008 NBA draft?",
    choices: ["Jason Collins", "O.J. Mayo", "Randy Foye", "Mike Miller"],
    correct: "O.J. Mayo",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these players were waived by the New York Knicks?",
    choices: [
      "Corey Brewer",
      "Brad Miller",
      "Malcolm Lee",
      "Quentin Richardson",
    ],
    correct: "Corey Brewer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which head coach did Chris Finch replace on the Minnesota Timberwolves?",
    choices: [
      "Flip Saunders",
      "Gersson Rosas",
      "Tim Connelly",
      "Ryan Saunders",
    ],
    correct: "Ryan Saunders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player led the league with 65 double-doubles in the 2008-09 season?",
    choices: ["Shaquille O'Neal", "Dwight Howard", "David Lee", "Ben Gordon"],
    correct: "David Lee",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player did the New York Knicks trade Tim Hardaway Jr. for?",
    choices: [
      "Jerian Grant",
      "Courtney Lee",
      "Brandon Jennings",
      "Damyeon Dotson",
    ],
    correct: "Jerian Grant",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In his last season with the New York Knicks, Patrick Ewing swept this team in the first round.",
    choices: [
      "Miami Heat",
      "Toronto Raptors",
      "New Jersey Nets",
      "Atlanta Hawks",
    ],
    correct: "Toronto Raptors",
  },
];

export const hardTF: TFQuestionType[] = [
  {
    question:
      "The three-point line was introduced to the NBA in the 1979-1980 season.",
    correct: "True",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "The NBA was founded in 1946 as the BAA (Basketball Association of America).",
    correct: "True",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Cleveland Cavaliers became a regular playoff contender by 2001",
    correct: "False",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
  },
  {
    question: "Jarrett Culver was traded for Patrick Beverley",
    correct: "True",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Warriors played the Utah Jazz in the second roun of the 2006-07 playoffs",
    correct: "False",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Golden State Warriors beat the Utah Jazz to break the franchise record for most wins in a regular season.",
    correct: "True",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Golden State Warriors played their first game at the Chase Center in 2019.",
    correct: "True",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
  },
  {
    question: "Grayson Allen was traded for a first round pick.",
    correct: "False",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
  },
  {
    question: "The New York Knicks selected Rod Strickland in the first round.",
    correct: "True",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Scottie Pippen's previous team before the Bulls was the Portland Trailblazers.",
    correct: "True",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Michael Jordan finished the 1994 season leading the Bulls in every major statistical category.",
    correct: "False",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
  },

  {
    question: "The Chicago Bulls started their first three-peat in 1991.",
    correct: "True",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Landry Shamet and Mike Scott were traded together from the 76ers.",
    correct: "False",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
  },
  {
    question: "The New York Knick's third longest winning streak is 13.",
    correct: "True",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
  },
  {
    question: "The New York Knick's longest losing streak is 14.",
    correct: "False",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
  },
];
